When I find myself in times of trouble. Mother Mary comes to me
当我陷入困境时，圣母玛利亚来到我身边
Speaking words of wisdom, let it be. In my hours of darkness
说着智慧的话语，就顺其自然吧 在我黑暗的时刻
She is standing right in front of me. Speaking words of wisdom, let it be
她站在我面前 说着智慧的话语，就顺其自然吧
Let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be Whisper words of wisdom, let it be
顺其自然，顺其自然，顺其自然，顺其自然 耳语着智慧，就顺其自然吧
When all the broken hearted people Living in the world agree. There will be an answer, let it be
当世上所有心碎的人都同意时，会有答案，就顺其自然吧
For though they may be parted, There is still a chance that they will see. There will be an answer, let it be
即使他们可能分开 仍有机会相见 会有答案，就顺其自然吧
Let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be There will be an answer, let it be
顺其自然，顺其自然，顺其自然，顺其自然 会有答案，就顺其自然吧
Let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be Whisper words of wisdom, let it be
顺其自然，顺其自然，顺其自然，顺其自然 耳语着智慧，就顺其自然吧
And when the night is cloudy. There is still a light that shines on me, Shine until tomorrow, let it be
当夜幕笼罩时 仍有一道光辉照耀着我 照耀至明日，让一切顺其自然吧
And I wake up to the sound of music, Mother Mary comes to me Speaking words of wisdom, let it be
我在音乐声中醒来 圣母玛利亚来到我身边 说着智慧的话语，让一切顺其自然吧
Let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be Whisper words of wisdom, let it be
顺其自然，顺其自然，顺其自然，顺其自然 耳语着智慧，就顺其自然吧
Let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be There will be an answer, let it be
顺其自然，顺其自然，顺其自然，顺其自然 会有答案，就顺其自然吧
Let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be And there will be no sadness, let it be
顺其自然，顺其自然，顺其自然，顺其自然 那里将不再有悲伤，就顺其自然吧
And I wake up to the sound of music Mother Mary comes to me Speaking words of wisdom, let it be
我在音乐声中醒来 圣母玛利亚来到我身边 说着智慧的话语，让一切顺其自然吧